http://www.spiritualskyincense.com/privacy-policy

Menu
HomeShoppingAbout UsBeyond the BarnPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsContact Us
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Spiritual Sky collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.spiritualskyincense.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Spiritual Sky.
Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number,
Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookiesOur Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected informationSpiritual Sky collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To send periodic emails
The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides they would no longer like to receive emails from us the User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Changes to this privacy policy
Spiritual Sky has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Spiritual Sky
http://www.spiritualskyincense.com/
PO BOX 368 Kaitaia, 0440, NZ
Phone number: +64 9 408 0440
info@spiritualskyincense.com
Categories
Spiritual Sky IncenseSpiritual Sky ConesSpiritual Sky OilsAriki Gift IncenseAriki Scented Kete (sachet)Celestial Stars IncenseSolas Gourmet IncenseSpecials
Product Search
Category
AllSpiritual Sky IncenseSpiritual Sky ConesSpiritual Sky OilsAriki Gift IncenseAriki Scented Kete (sachet)Celestial Stars IncenseSolas Gourmet IncenseSpecials
Price From
Sort By
Sort by...DefaultAlphabeticalCodeLowest PriceHighest Price
Other Filters
On Special
In Stock
Connect With Us
View Cart
© Copyright 2020 Spiritual Sky Incense NZ, all rights reserved.
